Halperin, Rick; Papers apap108
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Rick Halperin Papers
1982-2000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap108
11.1 cubic ft.
Death penalty abolitionist who worked with many anti-death penalty organizations, capital defense attorneys, representatives of various communities of faith, newspaper editorial boards, victims' rights groups, members of the families of the condemned, and many death row inmates throughout the country.
Biographical Sketch
Rick Halperin is the Director of the Southern Methodist University Human Rights Education Program. Rick holds degrees from George Washington University, Southern Methodist University and Auburn University. He has also studied at The Sorbonne in Paris, France. Rick has held numerous positions of importance in organizations concerned with human rights and social justice. He is a past Chair of the Board of Directors of Amnesty International, USA. He served on the Board of Directors for several organizations, including the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP), Human Rights Initiative, Capital Punishment Investigation and Education Services, Jefferson-Titus Refugee Foundation, Center for Survivors of Torture and the International Rescue Committee. Rick's awards and recognition include: Amnesty International Frederick Douglass Abolitionist Award; Dallas Peacemaker of the Year; DCTV Freedom of Speech Award; NCADP Grassroots Activism Award; NCADP Lifetime Abolition Achievement Award; SMU Robert O. Cooper Fellowship in Peace and Justice. Rick has been a member of TCADP since 1998.
Since 1972, Rick Halperin has been actively involved in the effort and struggle to abolish the death penalty in the United States. He works with many anti-death penalty organizations, capital defense attorneys, representatives of various communities of faith, newspaper editorial boards, victims' rights groups, members of the families of the condemned, and many death row inmates throughout the country. He is president of the Texas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty. For more than a decade he has organized monthly anti-death penalty rallies in downtown Dallas. He was elected as a chairperson of the Board of Directors of Amnesty International USA from 1992 to 1993. Halperin operates the Web site Death Penalty News and Updates. He is also devoted to other areas of human rights and has been working with a variety of organizations that seek improvements in human rights.
In his personal statement on the Journey of Hope Web site, Halperin stated, "My entire life has been spent defending and advocating the idea that there is no such thing as a lesser person, and that all persons, regardless of whatever they have done, still have and remain worthy of their inherent dignity and must not, for any reason, be tortured or be put to death" [Halperin, Rich. "Rick Halperin's Bio". Journey of Hope, 2004. Accessed April 26, 2005]
Halperin still travels widely and speaks and monitors a variety of human rights concerns around the world. Over the past three decades, his uncompromising opposition to capital punishment has catapulted him to the forefront of the worldwide human rights movement.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains news clippings, newsletters, campaign materials, letters of plea, flyers and notices of rallies, research materials, organizational reports, and publications on the issue of the death penalty. The death penalty is documented in the U.S. as well as internationally including Europe, Iraq, Saudi Arabia, Cuba, Mexico, Vietnam, and China.
The major part of this collection is composed of news clippings, from 1982 to 2000. Rick Halperin collected news clippings on death penalty topics from diverse national and local newspapers, magazines, and websites, including media in other countries. The content of this news clipping collection is not limited to news reports on specific death sentence cases, but includes various statistical data and general opinions about the death penalty, debates and controversies on execution methods, news reports on rallies pertaining to capital punishment, and human rights issues of prisoners. In addition, interviews with prisoners scheduled to be executed and photographs of victims, criminals, execution facilities, and capital punishment abolitionists are included in this collection.
Another interesting part of this collection is materials from Amnesty International USA (AI USA). As one of the leading organizations to work towards the abolition of the death penalty, this organization has produced and disseminated diverse materials, including mailings, magazines, handbook for AI USA trainers, and research papers on death penalty related topics. For instance, Amnesty International USA's Urgent Action is a letter of notification seeking demonstrative action to abolish execution. This letter provides background information on an upcoming execution case and recommended activities against the execution.
The collection lacks information on Halperin's personal activities as a professor at Southern Methodist University and research papers written by him that would show his opinions on the death penalty. Also, absent are documents that would illuminate Halperin's personal life. However, in this collection, there are several short notes, prepared by Halperin, for briefing of Amnesty International USA and correspondence between him and other death penalty abolitionists. A small number of news clippings contain news reports about Halperin and interviews with him.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized as follows:
Series 1: News Clippings, 1982, 1984-2000
Series 2: Court Reports, 1991-1999
Series 3: Court Files, 1988-1999
Series 4: Organization Files, 1984-2000
Series 5: Subject Files, 1982-1996
Series 6: Resource Files, 1983-2000
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by Rick Halperin in February 2001.
Separated Materials
Among the items collected by Halperin, materials owned by the University Libraries or available through interlibrary loan or online databases, were removed from the collection. However, items fitting this criterion that contain personal notes or letters were retained.
Items removed from collection:
Magazine:
The Crisis. New York: National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, v. 103, Issue 1, January 1996
Articles:
Albert, Craig J. "Challenging Deterrence: New Insights on Capital Punishment Derived from Panel Data". University of Pittsburgh Law Review, v. 60, Issue 2 (Winter 1999), 321-371.
Bright, Stephen B. "The Electronic Chair and the Chain Gang: Choices and Challenges for America's Future". Notre Dame Law Review, v. 71 (1996), 845-860.
Freedman, Eric M. "Innocence, Federalism, and the Capital Jury: Two Legislative Proposals for Evaluating Post-Trial Evidence of Innocence in Death Penalty". New York University Review of Law and Social Change, v. 18 (1990-91), 315-324.
Ledewitz, Bruce. "The Morality of Capital Punishment: An Exchange". Duquesne Law Review, v. 29, No. 4 (Summer 1991), 719-731.
Megivern, James J. "Our National Shame: The Death Penalty and the Disuse of Clemency". Capital University Law Review, v. 28 (2000), 595.
Mello, Michael. "Adhering to Our Views: Justices Brennan and Marshall and the Relentless Dissent to Death as a Punishment". Florida State University Law Review, v. 22, no. 3 (Winter 1995), 591-694.
Mello, Michael. "Defending Death". American Criminal Law Review, v. 32, no. 4 (Summer 1995), 933-1012.
Mello, Michael. "Raising Holy Hell: John Brown's Trial Lawyers (and Ted Kaczynski's Lawyers) and the Politics of the Insanity Defense". Criminal Law Bulletin, 1998, 279-327.
Mello, Michael. "The Real Capital Punishment: (Shotgun) Marriage Between Social Science and Litigation, and the Inviting Footnote in Brown v. Texas". Criminal Law Bulletin, March-April 1999, 107-126.
Paduano, Anthony and Stanford Smith, Clive A. "Death Errors: Juror Misperceptions Concerning Parole in the Imposition of the Death Penalty". Columbia Human Rights Law Review, v. 18 (1987), 211-257.
Reinhardt, Stephen. "The Anatomy of an Execution: Fairness vs. Process". New York University Law Review, v. 74, no. 2 (May 1999), 313-353.
Ross, Michael B. "It's Time for Me to Die: An Inside Look at Death Row". The Journal of Psychiatry & Law, v. 26 (Winter 1998), 475-491.
Tabak, Ronald. "Penal Discussions: Human Rights and Human Wrongs: Is the United States Death Penalty System Inconsistent with International Human Rights Law?" Fordham Law Review, v. 67, no. 6 (1999), 2793-2825.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Social Activists and Public Advocates; Death Penalty; Criminal Justice and Prisons; Capital punishment.; Capital punishment -- Law and legislation -- United States -- History.; Death row.; Human rights workers.; Halperin, Rick; Amnesty International USA.; American Civil Liberties Union.; Death Penalty Information Center (U.S.); NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund.
- News Clippings, 1982; 1984-2000; 1; 8.5 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  Series 1 consists of news clippings and magazine articles related to the death penalty issue, notices of rallies, fliers, and pleas written by death penalty abolitionists. The original order of materials, accumulated and grouped together by Halperin, was maintained.
  The bulk of series 1 is news clippings and magazine articles. News clippings were photocopied on acid free paper and oversized news clippings were stored in original format covered by acid free papers. Several items, originally created in fax format, were scanned, modified, and printed on acid free paper because of severe paper deterioration. Included are several news clippings collected from newspapers in other countries, including France and Italy.
  The news clippings from April 1990 to December 2000 are organized on a monthly basis. However, materials from March 1994 to December 1995 are grouped by individual death row cases.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  - News Clippings, 1982 (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1984 (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1985 (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1986 (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1989-February 1990 (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1990 April (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1990 May (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1990 May (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1990 June (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1990 July (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1990 August (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1990 September (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1990 October (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1990 November (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1990 December (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1991 January (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1991 February (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 1991 March (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, 1991 April (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 20)
  - News Clippings, 1991 May (Box 1 (1-News Clippings), Folder 21)
  - News Clippings, 1991 June (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1991 July (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1991 July (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1991 August (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1991 August (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1991 September (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1991 September (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1991 October (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1991 October (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1991 November (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1991 November (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1991 December (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1992 January (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1992 January (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1992 February (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1992 February (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1992 March (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1992 March (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 1992 April (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, 1992 April (Box 2 (1-News Clippings), Folder 20)
  - News Clippings, 1992 April (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1992 May (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1992 May (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1992 June (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1992 July (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1992 August (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1992 August (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1992 September (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1992 October (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1992 October (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1992 November (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1992 December (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1993 January (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1993 January (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1993 February (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1993 March (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1993 April (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1993 May (Box 3 (1-News Clippings), Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 1993 June (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1993 June (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1993 July (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1993 July (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1993 August (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1993 August (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1993 September (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1993 October (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1993 October (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1993 November (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1993 December (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1994 January (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1994 February (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1994 February (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1994 March-1994 September (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1995 (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1996 January (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1996 January (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 1996 February (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, 1996 February (Box 4 (1-News Clippings), Folder 20)
  - News Clippings, 1996 March (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1996 March (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1996 April (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1996 May (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1996 June (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1996 July (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1996 August (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1996 September (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1996 September (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1996 October (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1996 November (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1996 December (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1997 January (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1997 February (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1997 March (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1997 April (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1997 April (Box 5 (1-News Clippings), Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1997 May (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1997 May (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1997 June (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1997 June (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1997 June (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1997 July (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1997 July (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1997 August (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1997 September (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1997 October (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1997 October (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1997 November (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1997 December (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1997 December (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1998 January (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1998 January (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1998 February (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1998 February (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 1998 March (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, 1998 March (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 20)
  - News Clippings, 1998 April (Box 6 (1-News Clippings), Folder 21)
  - News Clippings, 1998 April (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1998 May (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1998 June (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1998 June (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1998 July (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1998 July (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1998 August (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1998 August (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1998 September (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1998 September (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1998 October (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1998 October (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1998 November (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1998 November (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1998 December (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1999 January (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1999 January (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1999 February (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 1999 February (Box 7 (1-News Clippings), Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, 1999 March (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1999 April (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1999 May (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1999 May (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1999 June (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1999 June (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1999 July (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1999 July (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1999 August (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1999 August (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1999 September (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1999 October (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1999 November (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1999 December (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 2000 January (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 2000 February (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 2000 March (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 2000 April (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 2000 May (Box 8 (1-News Clippings), Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, 2000 June (Box 9 (1-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 2000 June (Box 9 (1-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 2000 July (Box 9 (1-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 2000 August (Box 9 (1-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 2000 September (Box 9 (1-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 2000 October (Box 9 (1-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 2000 November (Box 10 (1-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 2000 December (Box 10 (1-News Clippings), Folder 2)
- Court Reports, 1991-1999; 2; 0.33 cubic ft.
  This series is a collection of photocopied court reports on death sentence cases from 1991 to 1997. These records were collected from Federal Reporter, 2nd or 3rd Series, Daily Appellate Report, and California Supreme Court. These records provide information on each death row case argued and determined in the United State Courts of Appeals.
  These records are arranged chronologically, based on the date of execution or the record publication date. The documents from 1997 to 1999 are incomplete and there are several gaps in coverage. In several cases, the first page of a report is photocopied with the full page number reference. The full text is available in the University Libraries or through interlibrary loan.
  - Court Reports, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Court Reports), Folder 1)
  - Court Reports, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Court Reports), Folder 2)
  - Court Reports, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Court Reports), Folder 3)
  - Court Reports, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Court Reports), Folder 4)
  - Court Reports, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Court Reports), Folder 5)
  - Court Reports, 1996; 1997; 1999 (Box 1 (2-Court Reports), Folder 6)
- Court Files, 1988-1999; 3; 0.33 cubic ft.
  This series contains court documents on the clemency petition of Robert Harris in 1992 and the clemency petition of Terry Washington in 1997, as well as other court records of several death row cases from 1989 to 1999. Court records were prepared and served by official court reporters.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Clemency Petition of Robert Harris, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Court Files), Folder 1)
  - Clemency Petition of Robert Harris, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Court Files), Folder 2)
  - Clemency Petition of Robert Harris, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Court Files), Folder 3)
  - Clemency Petition of Terry Washington, 1997 (Box 1 (3-Court Files), Folder 4)
  - Gary Graham Case, United State Court of Appeals, 1988; 1992 (Box 1 (3-Court Files), Folder 5a.)
  - Joseph M. Giarratano Case, Supreme Court of the United State, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Court Files), Folder 5b.)
  - Kenneth Reed Smith Case, Opening and Closing Arguments, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Court Files), Folder 5c.)
  - Willie Lee Jester Case, Court of Common Pleas Franklin County, Ohio, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Court Files), Folder 6a.)
  - R. J. Van Hook Case, Court of Appeals, First Appellate District Hamilton County, Ohio, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Court Files), Folder 6b.)
    and Letter from R. J. Van Hook to Abraham J. Bonowitz, 1994.